<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml version="2.0">
    <topic name= "jobs">
        <category>
            <pattern>JOBS</pattern>
            <template>
                Visualize a picture of a city in your mind. Are you standing in a nearby park 
                looking at the various skyscrapers, observing the traffic jams, utility vehicles 
                making their way around? Or are you driving one of those utility vehicles, one of those 
                stuck vehicles, or perhaps working in one of the skyscrapers?<br/>
                Type "observing" or "participating".
            </template>
        </category>
        
        <category>
            <pattern>I AM *</pattern>
            <template>
                <think><set name="city"> <star/></set></think>
                <condition name="city">
                    <li value="PARTICIPATING">
                        Now visualize a picture of a house. Do you first think about how it is constructed, 
                        or do you imagine all the possible things that could go wrong with owning one?<br/>
                        Say "construction" or "faults".
                    </li>
                    <li value="OBSERVING">
                        As an individual with a broad perspective on the overall operations of an entity, 
                        you tend towards a person with the skillset to manage those operations. A career in 
                        information technology project management would likely be ideal for you. An IT project manager 
                        oversees large-scale technology projects and managages the individual pieces that make up 
                        the project to ensure it is delivered on time and under cost. Your response regarding being 
                        an observer reflects a mind that can see both the big picture and the individual elements within.
                    </li>
                </condition>
            </template>
        </category>
        
        <category>
            <pattern>I THINK ABOUT ITS *</pattern>
            <template>
                <think><set name="house"> <star/></set></think>
                <condition name="house">
                    <li value="CONSTRUCTION">
                        When you think about the house's construction, do you imagine a blueprint or the physical parts?<br/>
                        Type "blueprints" or "parts"
                    </li>
                    <li value="FAULTS">
                        As an individual who takes a more deconstructive approach to solving problems, you would likely 
                        fit the role of a quality assurance engineer. A quality assurance engineer generally dedicates
                        his time to figuring out all the various ways he can break the code. Quality assurance is an integral 
                        part to the software development cycle because a team dedicated to finding issues prevents unforeseeable 
                        problems later down the road and saves company resources.
                    </li>
                </condition>
            </template>
        </category>
        
        <category>
            <pattern>I IMAGINE *</pattern>
            <template>
                <think><set name="house2"> <star/></set></think>
                <condition name="house2">
                    <li value="BLUEPRINTS">
                        When you imagine the blueprints, do you find yourself implementing existing 
                        blueprints, or do you see yourself as the individual who creates the blueprints?<br/>
                        Type "creating" or "following".
                    </li>
                    <li value="PARTS">
                        Based on your answers, you would likely make a talented hardware engineer. A hardware engineer 
                        researches, designs, and develops components to computer systems, such as the processors, circuit boards 
                        and memory devices. Your responses indicate a more "hands on" approach to working with computers where your 
                        focus is directed toward the physical aspects of design and development.
                    </li>
                </condition>
            </template>
        </category>
        
        <category>
            <pattern>I SEE MYSELF *</pattern>
            <template>
                <think><set name="house3"> <star/></set></think>
                <condition name="house3">
                    <li value="CREATING">
                        As an individual who designs the foundational tools and expands the amount of knowledge available, you 
                        would likely make a successful computer and information research scientist. This is an expert in the field 
                        of computer science and usually requires making your way to a PhD. It is a hefty investment in time, but 
                        the rewards are limitless as you would work on the forefront of technology. The information and research 
                        scientist spends less time writing code and more time studying discrete mathematics and computation theory.
                    </li>
                    <li value="FOLLOWING">
                        Based on your answers, you look to have the mind for a career in software engineering.
                        A software engineer takes a constructive approach to solving problems in the abstract, 
                        while conceptualizing the inner workings of a project in terms of blueprints and 
                        abstract objects that inherit from those blueprints.<br/>
                        Your responses indicate the kind of creative and abstract thinking software engineers 
                        employ for developing all types of software products.
                    </li>
                </condition>
            </template>
        </category>
        
        <category>
            <pattern>BLUEPRINT</pattern>
            <template>
                
            </template>
        </category>
    
    </topic>
</aiml>